What do you think?
你怎么想?
I think something's caught in here.
我想这里有东西卡住了.
I mean, what do you think of running?
我是说, 你对竞选是怎么想的?
For office?
竟选公职?
No, Boston Marathon. Yes, for office.
不, 参加Boston马拉松. 是的, 是竟选公职.
I'm not sure. I love my job.
我不知道. 我喜欢我的工作.
But, I've been there for eight years.
但是, 我已经在那里干了8年了.
Maybe it's time to move on.
也许是该离开的时候了.
Maybe it's time for a new job.
也许是换新工作的时候了.
Ah, but you won't know you have this job until the election.
Ah, 但是你必须先当选, 才算是得到了这份新工作.
True. You know, the thought of public office never occurred to me.
说得对. You know, 我以前从来没想过做公职.
But ever since Constanza's phone call, it's been on my mind.
但自从接到Constanza的电话之后, 我就在想这事.
What do you think?
你的意见呢?
I don't think that goes there.
我认为那东西不该放在那里.
Isn't the belt supposed to go there?
皮带不是应该放在那里吗?
Well, I think it's very exciting.
Well, 我想那会很令人兴奋.
But I'm worried too.
但我也很担忧.
I mean, this will have an enormous effect on all of us.
我是说, 这对我们都会有很大的影响.
For instance, our lives will certainly change during a campaign.
比如说, 我们的生活在竞选过程中肯定会发生变化.
Are you listening?
你在听吗?
For instance, our lives will certainly change during a campaign.
比如说, 我们的生活在竞选过程中肯定会发生变化.
You're doing it again.
你又来了.
What?
什么?
You repeat what I say, but you don't really hear it.
你重复我所说的话, 但却没有真正听进去.
Sweetheart, you think I can't hear unless I look at you.
亲爱的, 你认为我只有看着你才听得见.
But in fact, I use my ears to listen, not my eyes.
但事实上, 我是用耳朵听, 而不是用眼睛听.
I can even hear you with my eyes closed.
我闭着眼晴也听得见你说的话.
Go ahead. Say something.
接着讲. 说点什么.
You're impossible.
真拿你没办法.
I'm impossible. See?
拿我没办法. 你瞧?